Okay, so I showed you how to do it using
async and a wait. Let's do it using
then. So if I want to do this, I'd call
my wait function and I'd wait 3 seconds
and then um that returns a promise. So I
could either say let promise
equal wait and then I could say
promise.n
or since it returns a promise, I can
just directly chain the then onto the
end of this wait. So, I can say wait
3,00 seconds or sorry, 3,000
milliseconds, not 3,000 seconds. That
would take forever. Uh, wait 3,000
milliseconds, then take the value it
returns and console.log the value. So,
the value that we're receiving here,
remember, then takes a function. That
function takes in a parameter. That
parameter that it receives is from the
resolve function. So, this then runs if
it resolves. Well, what if it rejects?
Um, in the last one we used try and
catch to do it. Well, thankfully they
built that in here too. So you'd say
wait then do this and then on the end
you tag on the word catch and it
receives an error which you can then
console.log.
So I'm saying wait 3,000 milliseconds.
Then if it's successful log out what you
got back. If it's not successful log out
the error. So
now if we come over here we get big
scary error waits 1 2 3
big scary error and so it waits the 3
seconds and then because we called
reject rather than doing this then it
goes straight to the catch. So it try
it's similar to how this try catch works
where catch can receive an error and you
can log it out. This catch also receives
an error and you can log it out. And so
if you tag catch onto the end of your
chain of dotns, then um you can handle
errors as they appear.